<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<id>urn:uuid:d7e43e4b-8da4-4214-a13d-c6c2a489f6cd</id>
	<title>AltDrag</title>
	<link href="http://altdrag.googlecode.com/svn/wiki/feed.xml" rel="self" />
	<link href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/" />
	<updated>2009-04-24T13:37:00Z</updated>
	<author>
		<name>Stefan Sundin</name>
		<email>recover89@gmail.com</email>
	</author>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:a3154d04-2e39-4508-8146-2c77817ab951</id>
		<title>AltDrag - 0.7</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/" />
		<updated>2009-04-24T13:37:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
Released 0.7.&lt;br/>
This version adds the ability to roll-up windows by double-clicking with the middle mouse button. I've also added a new feature called &lt;tt>StickyScreen&lt;/tt> which makes windows automatically stick to the screen borders without needing shift. This only works with the Alt button unless you enable &lt;tt>ExperimentalFeatures&lt;/tt>.&lt;br/>
I have also fixed a few bugs with &lt;tt>ExperimentalFeatures&lt;/tt>, so it's working really well now, give it a try.&lt;br/>
In addition to that I've fixed a couple of small bugs, including an error message that sometimes popped up if you had AltDrag on autostart.&lt;br/>
I've also updated the installer, so upgrading should be a breeze.&lt;br/>
&lt;br/>
&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/recovers-tools">&lt;img src="http://altdrag.googlecode.com/svn/wiki/groups.png"/> Discuss in the forum.&lt;/a>
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:fb421892-2db6-46db-89d8-dced59442005</id>
		<title>AltDrag - 0.6</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/" />
		<updated>2009-02-12T16:30:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
Released 0.6.&lt;br/>
This version fixes some small bugs, most notably one which made AltDrag ignore the &lt;tt>-hide&lt;/tt> switch. It also adds the sticky behavior to resizing. There's a new language as well, Korean, thanks to 김장환 Jang-hwan Kim!&lt;br/>
This version should no longer have any false positives on antivirus scanners since I no longer compress with upx.&lt;br/>
I hope you find that the update checker was useful, let me know if you have feedback or questions, either &lt;a href="mailto:recover89@gmail.com">via email&lt;/a> or post &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/recovers-tools">in the forum&lt;/a> (no registration required)!&lt;br/>
You can use the installer to overwrite the old version, there is no need to uninstall the old version in advance.
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:d92c3e9c-383a-4ae5-86bf-644261a043e8</id>
		<title>AltDrag - 0.5</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/" />
		<updated>2009-01-12T23:00:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
Released 0.5.&lt;br/>
It's been a while since the last version, but I think you'll like it. The highlights are: resizing, double-click to maximize, &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/wiki/Blacklist">blacklist windows&lt;/a>, changed mouse cursor during dragging/resizing. I hope those of you who have run into applications which have conflicts with AltDrag will help me create blacklist rules for them. AltDrag is now available in Spanish thanks to Fabrizio Ferri.&lt;br/>
I have also opened &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/recovers-tools"> a forum&lt;/a> which I hope you'll use to discuss AltDrag and my other tools, let me know what's good and what's bad.&lt;br/>
I have also gotten some reports that my tools show up on some antivirus scanners, these are all false positives! I will try to report it to the antivirus vendors.&lt;br/>
Finally, I would like to let you know that I have put donating details on the site, so if you feel this program is useful, please consider &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/wiki/Donate">donating money&lt;/a>.
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:d6721de7-7e4d-42df-9bcc-4722751b2620</id>
		<title>This feed</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/altdrag/" />
		<updated>2008-09-24T14:30:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
Hi everyone.&lt;br/>
This feed will let you know when there's any update to AltDrag.&lt;br/>
There's also another feed available &lt;a href="http://superf4.googlecode.com/svn/wiki/all.xml">here&lt;/a> which will let you know if there's an update to any of programs.&lt;br/>
You can take a look at all my programs &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/u/recover89/">here&lt;/a>.
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>